- Must be 50: 50, Luang Pho.
- Hey,
And I ...
So what will the temple get?
When the new church was completed,
you held another ceremony.
But if not, I help push it.
The budget would not come down to the temple like this.
Found it under the base of the Buddha statue.
One hundred thousand.
Isn't it too little?
It has to be shared with him.
Unless, he will go and talk.
We will have to return the government's property soon.
The government staff is sitting here.
Two hundred thousand.
Is it enough?
Then you think about it again.
It's so damn hard.
Who's that?
If you are busy with me,
You will die.
Is it yours?
Hey,
Oh,
You go to tell the village headman.
He'll meet me.
Hoy!
(PREY)
The buddha doesn't protect the devil like you.
Luang Pho,
In this case, the police officer
gives weight in terms of murder.
Because traces of fighting were found
Including evidence that
The deceased monk had been drinking and socializing with someone before the tragedy occurred.
There are several possible causes of the murder.
Both the temple corruption scandal and the ancient dagger that was recently discovered.
But disappeared without a trace.
Thep,
Thep, wake up.
Wake up.
Are you dreaming of a girl?
I don't have any classes today, do I?
Yes, but today we have something to do. If we don't go, Mom will be angry.
Okay.
Wake up.
Hurry up.
Since we have tried everything,
We can try some mothers' methods, it's okay.
I just felt that it was not fair with him.
Like bringing him to raise.
For us to have children jealous
And I don't like to call our children as jealous child.
Even though he hasn't born yet.
Let's not be too serious about just a nickname.
And another thing, I agreed with Mom.
Because the two of us intend to support the children.
And if we have our own children.
This child is still a child that
we want and will never leave him.
Okay,
It depends on you.
Because of your happiness is my happiness.
So let's go.
What's up?
Nothing.
Now there are 129 children with us.
Age from newborn to 17 years.
We separate the children into age groups.
- For this group, will be 5-7 years old.
- Um.
Most adoptive parents will
come to pick up since they're a baby.
Um.
And the children who do not have a sponsor.
Must be here forever?
We will take care and send them to study until graduate.
Then they will go out to live like normal people.
But some people come back to help with the work here.
Can you smile?
Can you laugh?
Are you hungry now?
Very cute.
Her name is Chan Chao.
5 years old.
She was born in the full moon night.
Mother therefore named Chan Chao.
She live with us for a year.
And where is her mother?
Now, the mother is receiving treatment.
The doctor assessed that
she is unable to take care of her child.
So we have to separate the child.
If all documents are ready, we'll contact you back.
Thank you.
Hello,
Did the director tell them about Chan Chao?
Go.
Calm down.
Director,
Maybe what Chan Chao's mother said was true all along.
How can you trust what a sick person says?
Go prepare Chan Chao's documents.
Chan,
You'll fall soon. Come down.
Say hello to Grandma.
Hello,
Grandmother.
Cute, right?
Hurry and bring your brother soon.
Seems to be naughty.
Your arms are all green.
Okay, all sleep.
Go.
When she's not here, I miss her too.
I miss her, but once I think about it
I'd rather sleep soundly
and not wake up terrified at night.
What are you playing? Is it the right time?
Just a little.
- Where are you going?
- Go to sleep.
When the dwarf back home.
They found Snow White's lifeless body lying on the floor.
The dwarf then quickly pulled out the hair pin.
And that caused Snow White to breathe again.
Hey,
Still not sleeping yet?
I'm reading a bedtime story.
Let daddy read it?
I'll read it.
The queen asked the mirror as soon as she returned to the palace.
The magic mirror tells me.
Who is the most beautiful in the world?
It's okay. It was just a lightning strike.
It's okay.
You're okay.
- Let's daddy read the story.
- I'll continue to read.
Who is the most beautiful in the world?
Once again, the magic mirror answered that,
The queen.
- Oh.
- Oh, oh.
- Don't be scared, just lightning.
- Daddy and Mommy are here.
Listen carefully to the story so you can forget about the lightning.
Come to the queen.
The queen was angry.
- Mommy,
- Yes.
Have you finished working?
Not yet.
If finished, can you read the story?
- Yes, but let me finish the work first, okay?
- Yes,
I'll read it for you.
Okay.
This story.
When she's growing up a little more, be more careful.
That's it.
Thep love Chan Chao like his own daughter.
There is no story like you think.
No matter how much you love and care for her, she is not your own blood.
This is a friendly warning.
Mother,
Have you forgotten that it was you who insisted on us picking up the child?
Uh,
And then.
Don't have any signs yet?
Oh, Nid saw the money in the garbage.
The pocket.
At that moment, when my pocket was full of money, She wanted many things and many things popped into her head.
If the money were ours,
we could buy anything we wanted.
I think...
I want her to go to school next year.
A little slower than others, it's fine.
But I would like to teach her myself.
Also, I want to spend
more time to get to know each other first.
Otherwise, when entering school.
We probably only spend a few hours together a day.
And how about you?
Do you want to go to school?
Yes, I want.
Ouch!
- Chan Chao,
I told you.
How are you?
Does it hurt?
It's okay.
I'll go put some medicine on it. It'll be fine.
It's fine.
You just wanted to eat steak and make it a mess.
What sound is this?
Who opened the shop so loudly?
Actually, we check all the cameras that there is nothing.
But if you are still uncomfortable.
I can call people to add more cameras.
Thank you.
So strange.
Why does the blood still not stop flowing?
She has hemophilia.
It's a genetic disease.
She'll have a difficult bleeding, difficult to stop.
Be careful not to get a bump or fall.
Because it's easy to bruise.
And there is bleeding under the skin.
Yes,
Mother,
Okay, now that we're done, shall we go home?
Go.
Be careful
You haven't told me yet.
What did the doctor say?
- The doctor said she has hemophilia.
- Hemophilia?
It is a genetic disease.
Doctors call this disease "bleeding easy but hard to stop".
And the body is easily bruised,
it is a symptom of this disease.
I therefore thought that she would have a home school.
Until she's big enough to take care of herself better.
Are you still hurt? Be careful.
- What color do you want?
- How about the hat to be orange?
Let's eat snacks first.
Thank you mom.
- May I go to the bathroom first.
- Yes.
Oh, it is so beautiful.
- Do you like it?
- Yes, I do.
- Are you having fun?
- Yes, I am.
Why don't you raise her to be like a princess?
Even having a teacher come to your home for tutoring.
Let's go and play there first.
Mother,
You know why.
How many years has it been?
My own grandchildren have not been born once.
While also having to raise children with strange diseases.
You should return her back.
Mother,
We can raise puppies and kittens.
These are all people.
Come on, Mommy will swing you.
- Take it hard.
- Yes,
Is it fun?
Yes,
More harder?
It's fun.
Sister,
Do you want it?
I'll share it with you.
It's delicious. Take it.
Crazy girl.
Mother hires a special teaching.
When I'm getting older than this, I'll go to school.
Why can't you go to school?
Mother said,
I bruise easily and bleed easily.
Black bruise.
Mother is scared of me
to be naughty at school and wound.
If I take care myself, I can go.
So you're very naughty.
A little bit.
What should I do?
Who is outside?
Did you hear me?
Who is outside, open the door for me.
Ouch!
Oh my gosh, what is this?
Anyone outside, please open the door for me.
Can you hear me? Who's outside?
Open the door.
I think the housekeeper who came to clean.
He might have put up a defamatory picture.
But it like being thrown out
And also the door.
I has been snatched for a long time.
It's like someone locked outside.
You're making this face like you don't believe me, right?
And what do you think is the cause, Mom?
Mother,
This is our own home. There is nothing.
In the past, there was nothing.
But are you really not noticed?
That since we've Chan Chao,
Our house has more strange things every day.
Mother,
Don't be prejudiced,
Both of you,
No one believes me.
How is Grandma?
Yes, does it rain a lot in Songkhla? I've never been there. I've only been to Phuket.
Yes.
If I'm free, I'll invite Ploy to travel.
Yes, we talk later. Goodbye.
It's almost finished.
But I don't know if there
will be a traffic jam. How about this?
If anyone arrives first, let's wait in the shop.
Okay,
Erm, don't have to take the car.
We'll get back together.
Yes.
- See you.
It's done. Let's go have dinner for your daddy's birthday.
So beautiful.
It's still less beautiful than you.
So sweet.
Shall we go?
Didn't you say you wouldn't go?
Lately, my luck has been down for some reason.
I heard that the shop you're going
to is next to the fortune teller's shop.
So I would like to go with you.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
Go.
Eat first.
Mother, I want to go to the bathroom.
Okay.
Oh, Ploy
Please help me buy some eclairs.
Luckily, we happened to be around here today. Then, I'll take Chan Chao to the bathroom myself.
Hurry and go.
Hurry up and come back.
Go, Grandma will take you to the bathroom.
Grandmother,
Mother,
Oh,
How was it?
Thep is coming to take you to file a report.
Please come with us so that you can provide information to the police. Because there are no CCTV here.
Okay, but it's strange.
Why didn't I see Chan Chao
when I came out of the bathroom?
Chan Chao,
Where have you been?
Where did you found her?
After I hang up with you and about to coming out.
The security guards brought her to me.
Then he said that a woman had brought her here.
A woman?
Sister.
Mother, mother.
Mother, I'm here.
Beautiful sister, but I don't know the name.
Chan Chao, how are...
Mother,
I can't breathe.
Be patient a little more.
We're close to the hospital.
I can't breathe.
Old lady.
This is just a lesson.
This kid?
- She has a spirit following her.
- Whose spirit is it?
If you don't hurry up and chase them away
This house is definitely going to hell.
So what should I do?
Chan Chao,
She said you asked her to pick up the earrings.
The child is delirious.
But she's not a liar.
Now I have no meaning in this house.
If you worship her so much,
then put her on a pedestal and worship her.
This is like going back to the beginning again.
Hey!
Thep, Thep, Thep.
Mr. Thep.
What are you doing here?
- The lady sent me to get you.
- I don't know how I got here.
Thep,
Where have you been?
Go to pay respect to uncle and aunt.
Can you remember me?
I'm glad to see you again.